<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>[MIS] - Arknights</name>
	<author>M.I.S. Group</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
		<li>1.6</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>MIS.Framework</packageId>
			<displayName>M.I.S - Framework</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/SamaraFleurety/Rimworld_Arknights</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>MIS.Framework</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description>
这是一款明日方舟同人模组
历经一年半的时间终于打磨成形，项目发起人墨鱼丸（蘑菇）
历经艰苦奋斗（指开发人员阳了个阳）终于发布

简介/
	这个mod为环世界增添了一个新的家具“招募台”
	玩家可以通过用白银手工加工点制作招募券来使用招募台，进行招募干员，我们准备了百余套优质干员时装
	干员不仅仅是干员服装，特性，属性，故事背景都和游戏剧情中一样，招募的干员将有血有肉加入殖民地与玩家互动

功能//
	mod实现了语音和立绘
	语音可以在设置中开关，可以设置反应时间
	（你可以把时间拉倒最短和琴柳玩琴流感）
	立绘功能（没啥好说的二次元）

常见问题///

	Q:可以中途加入/删除这个MOD吗
	A:几乎不可以中途删除。中途加入没有经过测试。建议新开档玩。

	Q:如何招募干员
	A:通讯技术科技 -> 手工加工点生产招募券 -> 建造招募台 -> 选择心仪的干员

	Q:我觉得xx干员贴图不好看
	A:画师会改但也请对现有的贴图保持理解
	画师都是未成年人，没有经过专业绘画训练

	Q:会有xx功能吗？
	A:如果合理或者有意思都会做，可以去创意工坊群提出意见或者建议

	Q:为什么干员没有语音/不显示立绘/立绘位置很奇怪
	A:MOD设置里面可以打开

	Q:干员贴图非常糊
	A:可以任意选用其他高清MOD.如:Vanilla Expanded Framework,然后MOD设置里关闭贴图缓存;也可以搜HD然后选自己喜欢的.

	Q:我想赞助本MOD/我会xml、c#、绘画，希望加入mod制作
	A:可以去创意工坊群留言或参与讨论

qq1群:383917697 (严禁键政)
qq2群:489397547 (比较自由)

本MOD目前处于测试阶段，没有经历过高压测试，有一定可能会导致坏档/闪退。建议新开档玩，并于出现bug提交反馈。

祝各位游戏愉快

This is a MOD inspired by mobile game Arknights.

A new buildable furniture “Recruit Console” is added.
Player can use it with recruit tickets(crafted at crafting spot) to recruit an operator from mobile game Arknights.
Currently we prepared 100+ operators with full set of apparel, weapon, trait, backstory and more.

Features//
Play operators' voice
Display operators' portrait
	Both are adjustable in Mod option

FAQ///
	Q:Can I add/delete this MOD in a play
	A:Delete this MOD in middle of a save is risky. Adding to exist save is also not tested. A new save is recommended.

	Q:How can I recruit an operator
	A:Microelectronics technology -> make a recruit ticket at crafting spot -> build a recruit console -> recruit your favorite operator
	
	Q:I think certain operator is ugly
	A:Illustrators will try to make every operator decent however please keep understands and tolerant to current textures.
	  Illustrators are all juveniles, did not received professional painting training.
	
	Q:Will this mod have certain feature?
	A:It is possible to add fan suggested feature/content if it is reasonable or attractive. Please leave your valuable comment at steam workshop.
	
	Q:Why my operators do not talk/do not have portrait/location of portrait is strange
	A:Switchs and adjustment are in MOD options.
	
	Q:Why textures of operators are in low resolution
	A:Use any HD MOD you like, for instance Vanilla Expanded Framework.
	
	Q:I have other suggestions
	A:Please leave them at steam workshop.

	Q:Certain place lacks English translate
	A:Apologize for any inconvenience. We currently do not have enough manpower to complete translation.
Warning: This MOD is currently at test phase, lacking of high pressure test, result in possibility to cause crash. Please do not play with a very valuable save, and report bugs.

Have a pleasant play with arknights operators!

开源协议/License: CC - BY - NC - SA

开发人员/Credits：
	主催:墨鱼丸
	美术:墨鱼丸，奈亚子
	程序:Fleurety，22，奈亚子
	数据库:盘子，FelixT，mude，3hst有限公司
	</description>
	<packageId>MIS.Arknights</packageId>
</ModMetaData>